For these latest updates now that you are
tracking.  We move forward with other
developments.  Shocking incident coming in
from Patna.  Where an ICICI
Lobards branch manager has been
identified as Abhishek Varun was found dead
in a well a long time ago with his scooter days after he was
reported missing.  His body was found during
the police investigation
into his disappearance.  His sleepers were
recovered from the field into the police
station area.  Raising the suspicious
input about the possible foul play and an
accident. He had attended a family function
in the Ramakrishna Nagar, staying back after his
family left. CCTV footage showed him
riding his scooter at 10:48 pm, appearing intoxicated.
Around 1:00 am, he called his
wife to report an accident, but his
phone was switched off shortly after.  Police
are also examining all the possible angles
including accident, intoxication,
potential foul play, and to determine the
exact cause of death.  Ritesh Mishra.  My
Colic Joints Me With The Latest Update.
What is this entire incident and how did this come
to the knowledge of the police personnel.
Ritesh, what more are you picking up?
Absolutely, this whole matter
seems quite suspenseful.  First he disappeared.
Then his wife
lodged an FIR regarding his disappearance.  The police took the whole matter
very lightly and last night his body was found in
Bur area of ​​Patna.  There is a well in a field.
His body was recovered from there.  His
scooter has been recovered from there and the police is
investigating.  Police
say that he was drunk and it is possible
that due to intoxication he might have fallen into the well or
his scooter might have slipped
and due to which he fell down.  But
his family members clearly say
that this is a murder because why would he come to this area
and the family
members are raising questions on the police station that
we had told them from the very first day that
something untoward could happen to him.  It is possible
that he might have been kidnapped or
something bad might have happened to him and the
apprehensions expressed by his family members have been
proved clear today and the
police is saying that we are
investigating this entire matter from all angles.  Now it remains to be
seen
what comes out of the investigation.  Well
alright on that note in fact Ritesh thank you very much while we move
forward with the top
developments in a significant development
the top